ACWA Education Department Records 5619/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- In Defense of Pennsylvania's Unemployed Workers, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Pennsylvania Congressional Districts, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  As of March 3rd
- Education, 1965-1970 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Legislative List, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Trade Union, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  Included: ILR 301 Course Syllabus; Union Label handbook
- Voting Records, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  Right to Work
- Abortion, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- ACWA - History, Structure, Function, 1947-1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- ACWA - Magazine Articles, 1963-1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- The Aging, 1962-1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- ACWA Retirement Members Newsletter, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Anti-Defamation League, 1967-1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Ministration, Union course outlines, etc., 1947-1948 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Alliance for Safer Cities, 1968-1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- American Friends Service Committee, 1959-1972 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- American Foundation for Continuing Education, 1957-1963 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- American Jewish Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Arbitration, 1949-1966 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Automation, 1956-1969 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Bibliographies, 1945-1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Bicentennial, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Budget, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Building Union Participation, 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1957-1971 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions - II, 1959-1972 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Civil Liberties, 1947-1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Civil Liberties - S1, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Concerning "Senate Bill 1," a proposed Criminal Justice Reform Act
- Civil Rights - Busing, 1968-1972 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Civil Rights - Civil Disorder, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Civil Rights - Democracy in Unions, 1958-1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Civil Rights - Discrimination in Housing, 1951-1967 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Civil Rights - Employment, 1957-1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Civil Rights - Generation I, 1964-1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Civil Rights - Generation II, 1949-1970 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- 1964 Civil Rights Bill, 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Civil Rights - Police & Justice, 1959-1971 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Civil Rights - School Integration, 1958-1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Civil Rights - South, 1960-1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Civilian Review Board, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  Concerning ballot initiatives targeting the New York City Civilian Review Board of the Police Department
- Collective Bargaining, 1949-1976 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Community Services, 1955-1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Congressional Reform, 1959-1964 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Constitution, 1948-1976 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  Concerning the United States Constitution but also contains the ACWA Constitution
- Consumer Problems, 1963-1975 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  Some Spanish language material - manual "precision shopping calculator"
- Course Outline, 1949-1967 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Crime - Criminal Justice, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  Memos on the Criminal Justice Reform Act: February - March
- Day Care Centers, 1967-1977 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Depressed Areas, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Discussion Groups, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Dissent, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Economics, 1958-1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Higher Education, 1965-1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Education - General, 1963-1975 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Education - Financing, 1961-1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Education - Labor, 1959-1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Presidential Election - 1976 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  Carter - Ford
- Election - 1964, 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  Johnson - Goldwater
- Election 1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  Some Spanish language material
- Elections 1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  Humphrey - Nixon
- Election 1972, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  McGovern - Nixon; Watergate Scandal
- Elections 1977 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  March 1977
- Employment - General, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  "An Action Program to Put America Back to Work," January 23, 1975
- Imports, 1952-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Insurance, 1950-1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- International, 1955-1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Job Retraining, 1962-1965 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Job Applications, 1968-1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Labor Bookshelf, 1965-1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Labor History, 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Labor History - II, 1939-1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Labor Law Reform, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Labor - South, 1937-1960 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Labor Theatre, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Mergers, 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Military-Industrial Complex (Anti-Ballistic Missiles), 1969-1977 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  Includes another folder entitled Military Spending Defense [illegible]
- Minimum Wage, 1961-1977 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Monopoly, 1959-1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- National Policy on Aging, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  November 28 - December 2 White House Conference on Aging
- National Labor Relations Board, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- National Planning Association, 1969-1973 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Negro History, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  January 1969
- Newspapers - Miscellaneous Locals, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Occupational Safety, 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Parliamentary Procedure, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  Includes older but undated documents
- Peace, 1950-1977 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Trade Union Division of SANE, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Peace - Vietnam, 1954-1974 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- International Women's Year, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  The Interdependent, newsletter of the United Nations Association, January 1975
- Peace - Fall-Out, Radiation, 1959-1968 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Peace Corps, 1962-1969 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Steward Materials - Structure of ACTWU - Dues (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Forms and educational materials
- Grievance (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Contract - Grievance (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Labor Law - Fair/Unfair Representation (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Collective Bargaining - Steward Materials (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Collective Bargaining - Arbitration - Discipline/Discharge - Fringe Benefit (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Arbitration - Apparel Industry-Male - Cotton Garment Industry - Retail-Trade Terms, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Union Building Materials - Organizing Materials (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Union Building Materials (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Union Building - Constitution - Local Union Officers (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Writing-Education Material - Speech (Box 28, Folder 11)
  Forms and educational material
- Health and Safety - Labor Political Activities (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Correspondence - Clayola Brown, 1979-1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- General Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Two, 1971-1976 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  N.Y. Headwear Unity Joint Board pin
- Headwear and Allied Workers Joint Board, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  Flyers and educational materials
- South Carolina Coastal, 1977-1980 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- William Elkus, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Sol Stetin, 1979-1983 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1981-1984 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Bruce Raynor, 1979-1983 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Bruce Dunton, 1979-1984 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Joe Coponi, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Joyce Miller, 1981-1987 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous: Reports/Flyers/Newsletter/Conferences/Workshops, 1971-1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Flyers and educational materials; also contains folder entitled: Bi-County Joint Board Conference (VPI) Donaldson Brown Center, Blacksburg VA. May 26-29, 1983
- The Agitator, 1982-1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- The Challenger, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Changing Times - Local #2268, 1984-1989 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Fredericksburg Office News - Locals #1645, 2422, 2092, 658, 1398, 713, 844 - Upper South Regional Joint Board, 1982-1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Cone Workers - "Union Voice", 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- "The Electric Blanket" - Local #1950 - Belton, South Carolina, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Fog Bull, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  June Newsletter, Volume 1
- Forum - Toronto Joint Board, 1978-1983 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board - The Organizer, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- "Bargain" In Good Faith, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- The American Labor Museum - Botto House, 1982-1990 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- "Action" - South California Joint Board, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Actor Unity - The Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Organization of Retirees, 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Cut Sheet - Pacific Northwest Joint Board, 1982-1986 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- ACTWU In Southern Virginia - Locals #1335; 2417; 2037; 2024 - Narrows, Virginia, 1983-1987 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Labor Power - Local #2280 - Sylvester, Georgia, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- ACTWU - Needle's Eye, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- ACTWU Seniority (Newsletter), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO News, 1979-1989 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  Newspaper clippings with a photograph of ACTWU President Jack Sheinkman and the Rev. Jesse Jackson
- "Advance" - ACTWU In Action, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- "Keynote's" - Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Labor Leadership - ACTWU Staff, 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Labor - News and Views - GTA Area Joint Board, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  November 1984
- Labor Times - Chicago and Central States, 1982-1987 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- L'Aiguille, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  English-French newsletter
- Making Progress - Voice of the Samsons and Delila Workers, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Amalgamated News - Philadelphia Joint Board, 1981-1987 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Amalgamated Retired Members Newsletter, 1976-1983 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 1977-1989 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Headwear Worker, 1982-1986 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- The Hopeful Times, 1985-1988 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- The Informer, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Independent Office Employees Union Express, 1978-1981 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Boll Weevil - Local #1716 - Rome, Georgia, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  January 1984
- The Local Union Voice - Wallace, North Carolina, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  March 1982
- Hanes Workers' Voice - Galax, Virginia, 1981-1983 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- "Hanes Worker" (Newsletters), 1983 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- The Happening, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  Newsletter, March 9, 1985
- Local Union Express - Twin Cities Joint Board, 1977-1982 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Hard Times - Local #335, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- "The Union Express" - Locals #473, #1807, #1708, #385, #317, #294T, 1976-1988 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Wellman Display Windows - Johnsonville, South Carolina, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Action (Box 30, Folder 2)
  Congressional District Committees
- The Stevens Worker, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  July 1978
- Talking Union - New England Regional Joint Board, 1983-1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Under the Hat, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- "Rocky Mountain Hi" - Rocky Mountain District Joint Board, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  October 1983
- Shoe Horn - Local 206A, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  November 1983
- The Shoemaker's Bench - Upper South Regional Join Board (Locals #1776; 1777; 1784; 1841; 2330), 1983 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Solidarity - Cap Maker's Union: 2H ACTWU, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- "Solidarity Advocate" - Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Southwest Progress - Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Southern Unity, 1986-1988 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Synthetics and Film Division - Fiber Facts Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Blue Ribbon News - Local 844-T, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- The Agitator, 1985-1988 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Network News - ACTWU Social Services Committee, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  Spring 1979
- The New Edition, 1983-1989 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- The New 340 Leader - Local 340 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- News and Views - Local #1018, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- The Newsletter - Local 1362 - Ella Ford, President, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  October 1987
- "The News Pad" - Local 1901, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- The Phoenix Eagle - Andrews, South Carolina - Unchartered, 1981-1990 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- "Powder News" - Ohio State Joint Board, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Reflections - Rochester Joint Board, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Rip and Stitch Denim Blus (Newsletter) - Local 731, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Rochester Joint Board - "Reflections", 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Roanoke Valley Joint Board, 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Talk of the Town - South Alabama Sub Regional Office, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- The Target Worker's Voice (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Tennessee Textile Workers - Local #281, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- "US" - Tri-County Joint Board (?), 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Unity Report - Roanoke Valley Joint Board, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  January 1985
- United Times - Local 2500, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Union Pride - Local 118-C, 1987-1989 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Union Monthly Times - (Craddock-Terry) Tidewater Joint Board - Farmville, Virginia, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Local #288 - The Needler - San Diego, California (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Local #281 - "Union Newsline", 1983-1989 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Local #254, 1976-1980 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Local 226C - Union News Highlights (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Local 177 News New England Regional Joint Board, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  Brief Spanish language material
- "The Shoe String" - Local #146-SW, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Local 80 - Newsletter Update, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  Includes material from Local #80T
- Local #63H - Off the Top of Our Heads - Denver, Colorado, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  April 1983
- Local #14F, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- Local #3 News - Rochester, New York, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- Wilkes-Barre Newsletter - (Picnic for striking workers), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  Newsletter announcing a picnic August 26, 1979 in support of the Wilkes-Barre strikers
- West Coast Regional Joint Board - (Newsletter), 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  Newsletter is entitled "Voice"
- Wage Voices - Locals 958; 1437; 1893, 1976-1980 (Box 30, Folder 48)
- AFL-CIO News (Transcripts) - (Press Conferences), 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Forum - Toronto and Western Ontario Joint Boards, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Ethical Practices Code of TWUA, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- TWUA Instructors Outline for Parliamentary Procedure, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Handbook for TWUA Organizing Committees (Box 31, Folder 6)
- This is the House that TWUA Built (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Did You Know? (Flyer) - Public Education/Ten Hour Day/Vote/Bill of Rights (Box 31, Folder 8)
  Multiple copies of four different flyers
- They Said It Couldn't Be Done - TWUA History (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Sol Stetin Correspondence and Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Correspondence Clayola Brown, 1978-1989 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  Includes a color photograph and several photographic negatives
- Organizing Materials: Blitzers/Scabs, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- F.O.U.R. Contract - Clerical, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  The contract itself between FOUR and ACTWU was signed October 1, 1987
- Constitution of the South Carolina Coastal Joint Board (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Post-Hearing Brief of the Union Drug Testing Case Before the American Arbitration Association, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  May 24, 1986
- Visitors File, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated History - "Panorama" (Booklet), 1960 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Building a Union of Textile Workers Convention Report, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  May 15-19, 1939
- InterAmerican Textile, Leather, Garment and Shoe Workers Federation Caribbean Program (ACTWU), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  The acronym for Interamerican Textile, Leather, Garment and Shoe Workers Federation is FITITVC; April 21 - May 9, 1985
- Canvass 1984 Membership Survey Form (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Textile Industry: Kensington to Korea, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Textile Industry Lesson Plan, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Political Action (Lesson Plan), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Rieve-Pollock Foundation - Retiree Staff Reunion, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  November 10, 1984
- Directors Teaching Guide: Outline, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Speeches, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- State System of Higher Education - Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Special Project: Shell Boycott (Apartheid), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  February 1, 1986
- AFL-CIO South African Policy, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Southern Poverty Law Center - Montgomery, Alabama, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  Includes a color photograph of lynch victim Marvin Davis
- Industry Revisions, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Education Department Projection, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Textile Industry (Teaching Outline), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- (IAF) Industrial Area Foundation Training Program, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  July 26, 1984
- U.S. Supreme Court Ruling on Strikes, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- OSHA (Right-to-Know) Standards, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- Plant Closings Material, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- Jesse Jackson's Appeal to Democratic Party, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  July 17, 1984
- Economics, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- Quality of Work, 1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- Resolutions ACTWU Canada, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  June 18-20, 1979; in English and French
- Committee for Compensation for Pitts and Lee, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board Conference, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  June 21-24, 1979
- Labor Desk Study Tour - Portugal, Spain, Italy, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  June 17 - July 6, 1978
- Columbian Rope - Local 1085 - Auburn, New York, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Central and South Jersey Joint Board School (Rutgers), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  February 6, 1979
- Agreements TWUA, 1974-1977 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens (Worker-to-Worker) #4, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Agreements ACTWU, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens General Material, 1966-1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens: National Labor Relations Board and Legal Cases - (Legal History, etc.), 1965-1980 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- JPS Boycott: Articles, Letters, etc., 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- JPS Company Propaganda, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- JPS Company Work Rules (Box 32, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens Organizing Campaign, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- JPS Films, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- JPS Organizing Campaign (activities, reports, etc.), 1973-1976 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- JPS Organizing Campaign, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- JPS Worker-to-Worker Program, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- JPS OSHA Activities, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- JPS Miscellaneous (Correspondence, Press Releases, Newsletters), 1973-1979 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- JPS - Testimony of TWUA - Parts 1 and 2 before a subcommittee on labor-management relations, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  March 15, 1976, before the House of Representatives
- Bruce Raynor's File, 1973-1981 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Frank Nicholas - Bay Area Joint Board, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Bi-County Joint Board, 1947-1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Joseph Lipowski - Buffalo Regional Joint Board, 1973-1978 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- California Joint Board - Rothstein, Manager, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Charles "Bud" Clark - Canadian Joint Boards Reports, 1973-1982 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Carolinas-Virginia Regional Joint Board, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Catawba Valley Joint Board - Rock Hill, South Carolina (B. Ross, Manager), 1983 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Walt Rainey - Central Alabama-Georgia Joint Board, 1970-1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Ralph Coderre - Central Massachusetts Joint Board, 1974-1979 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board - G. Justice, Manager, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Central Penn Joint Board - McMahon, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Mike Merola - Central and South Jersey Joint Board, 1969-1980 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  Includes Spanish language materials
- Chicago Central States Joint Board (Clothing), 1973-1983 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Chicago Joint Board Area Industries Addresses, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Chicago Joint Board, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1969-1976 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, 1963-1973 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- ACTWU Cone Union Council - Greensboro, North Carolina (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Connecticut Joint Board, 1969-1976 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Delaware Valley Joint Board, 1974-1979 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- El Paso Joint Board - Ralph Ruiz, Manager, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- (ACW - Clothing Division) Florida Joint Board - Rosemary Reznicek, Manager, 1977-1982 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Garden Spot Joint Board - Carl Frazier, 1973-1983 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Georgia Joint Board - Oma Barton, 1981-1982 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Granite State Joint Board, 1969-1980 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board, 1968-1979 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Greater New York Joint Board, 1969-1976 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Great Northern Joint Board, 1977-1981 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- G.T.A. Area Joint Board - Chattanooga, Tennessee - Gerald Brown, 1970-1982 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Greater Toronto Textile Joint Board - Don Mills, Ontario, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1965-1982 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Headwear Joint Board - John Hudson, President, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Kansas City Joint Board, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Frank Nicholas - Los Angeles Joint Board, 1969-1978 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- Maine Joint Board - Lewistown, Maine - Denis Blais, Manager, 1969-1978 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  Includes a black and white photograph of several participants in the Saco Joint Board Leadership Training Program
- Midsouth Regional Office - Charlotte, North Carolina - (Walraven), 1982 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- ACW (Clothing Division) - Midwestern Joint Board, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  Letter from June 8, 1977
- Memphis Area Joint Board (Don Warner), 1973-1982 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- Minnesota Joint Board - Richard Honetschlager, manager, 1979-1983 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Manuel Fernandes - New Bedford Joint Board, 1973-1977 (Box 33, Folder 41)
- New England Regional Joint Board (Clothing), 1980 (Box 33, Folder 42)
- North Alabama Area Joint Board - Eula McGill, Manager, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  Memo from June 6, 1980
- North Carolina Central Joint Board (George Justice), 1973-1979 (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Northeastern Massachusetts Joint Board - Alton Hodgman, 1969-1979 (Box 33, Folder 45)
- Northern New Jersey Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 46)
- Ohio State Joint Board - Toledo, Ohio - Willis Opperman, 1978-1981 (Box 33, Folder 47)
- Pacific Northwest Joint Board, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 48)
- Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board - Ed Sherman, 1973-1981 (Box 33, Folder 49)
- Anthony DiCicco - Philadelphia Joint Board, 1969-1979 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  Includes a collection of color photographs
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 51)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board - Henry Dropkin, Manager, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  Memo from March 5, 1982
- Richard Gimmey - Portland Area Joint Board, 1970-1977 (Box 33, Folder 53)
- Jean-Marc Couture - Quebec Joint Board - Cowansville (Canada), 1979 (Box 33, Folder 54)
- Sam Azzinaro - Rhode Island Joint Board, 1960-1981 (Box 33, Folder 55)
- Roanoke Valley Joint Board - Clyde Bush, Manager, 1981-1982 (Box 33, Folder 56)
- Charles Sallee - St. Louis Joint Board, 1969-1980 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  Includes a color photograph of the board members
- David Rathke, International Representative - St. Louis Joint Board, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 58)
- Clothing Workers - ACW Scranton Joint Board, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  All material is handwritten
- Carl Frazier - Schuylkill Valley District Joint Board, 1975-1979 (Box 33, Folder 60)